Guide to the Records of the Tisch School of the Arts 1956-1981 (Bulk 1965-1981) RG 35
New York University Archives
- ACCESSION 93-025
  - Series V: Administrative Files
    - Subseries A: Administrative Files, con't.
      - Ford Foundation, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Gallatin Advisory Board, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Graduate Commission, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Grievance Committee, SOA (restructured; 1st Meeting), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - L-File, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Lampert, Rachel, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Legal Counsel, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - League for Professional Theater Training Program, undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Lefferts, George, undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Discipline Commission SOA, undated (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Levine, Naomi, undated (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Levine, Naomi, undated (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Levitt, Saul, undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226601 8
      - Calendar, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Jay Liebman Memorial Fund, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Library Elmer Homes Bobst NYU, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Linklater, Kirsten: Faculty, Department of Acting, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Lumet, Sidney, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - M-File: Mac-Mc, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - M-File, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Maitland, Ian, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Manoogian Memorial Fund, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Mann Scholars, undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Mannes College of Music, undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Ann Marcus, undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Markle, John and Mary Foundation, undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Markovich, Nick, undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Mayer Fellows, undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Mayer Foundation, undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Mayer, Louis B. Awards, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Chairman's Meeting, undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Faculty Meeting, undated (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Michelson, Annette, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226602 6
      - Miller J. Michael Assoc. Dean, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Miller J. Michael Assoc. Dean, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Miller J. Michael Assoc. Dean, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Milne, Charles, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Milne, Charles, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - MIT/TDR, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - TDR, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Mobil Film Festival, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Mobil Awards, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - MOMA, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Monteague Fund, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - William Morris Awards, undated (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Evangeline Morphos, undated (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Moss, Mitchell, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - O-File, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Office Equipment #1, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Oliva, L.J.: Provost, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Oliva Meeting Re: Photography, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Orientation Committee, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226603 4
      - N-File, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - National Direct Student Loan, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - National Endowment of Humanities, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - NEA, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - News Bureau Press Releases (NYU), undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - NY State art Dean Assoc., undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - NYU Rules and Regulation, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - P-File, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - P-File, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Painting and Sculpture NY Studio School, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Park, Jackie, undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Party: Faculty and Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Payton, Robert, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Pelfrey, Eugene, undated (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Penney, Mrs. J.C., undated (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - The Performance Group, undated (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Perry, Ted, undated (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Personnel, undated (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Photo Center, undated (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Polaroid, undated (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Poll, Martin, undated (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Prince, Harold, undated (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - NYU Press Brochures, undated (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Press, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Programs Abroad, undated (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 32)
      - Reading, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - R-File, undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226604 2
      - Real Estate, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Registrar, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Reiner, Carl, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Renovation, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Renovation: Final Report/Space Comm., undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Rochelle, Carlton, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Rockefeller, David, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Rodgers, Richard, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Rosenberg, Deena: MT Proposals Responses File 4, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Rosenberg, Deena: File 3, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Rosenberg, Deena, undated (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Rubinstein Foundation, undated (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Rubin, Samuel Foundation, undated (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - S-File: Sa-Schm, undated (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - S-File: Schn-Sh, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226605 9
      - S-File: Si-Sz, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Sakland, Maurice, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Scholarships, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Schechner, Richard, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Scherman Foundation, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Martin Segal, undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Seidman, J.S., undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Seidman, J.S., undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Seelman, Jo, 1980-1981 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Senate, undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Sequicentennial Festival, undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Sequicentennial: Miscellaneous/Altschuer, undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Shubert Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Shubert Organization Theater Program, undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Silvers, Sally, undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Simon, Elena, 1980 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Simon, Elena, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226606 7
      - Sklar, Robert, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Oliver, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Society of Fellows, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Sondheim, Steven, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Sony, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Space: SOA, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Space Alternative Media Interactive Telecommunication, undated (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Sponsored Programs, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Steinberg, Saul, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Stark, Peter (Memorial), undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Strasbouger, Samuel, undated (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Statistics: SOA, undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Stirk, David, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Stoney, George, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Student Affairs, undated (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Student Insurance Coverage, 1976-1979 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Student Organization, undated (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Summer Session: NYU and SOA, undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - T-File, undated (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - T-File, undated (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Tenure, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226607 5
      - Tuition Remission, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - U-File, undated (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - United Way, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - V-File, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - W: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Wank, Adams, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Warner Comm. Center, undated (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Warner Fellows, undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Brian Winston, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - WNYU, undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Young Audiences, undated (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - XYZ File, undated (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Grinnell, Janet: Development Job Description, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226608 3
      - Grinnell, Janet: Development Manager, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Gunderson, Karen: Faculty, Department of Drama, Undergraduate, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - H-File, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Hoffman, Ted: Director, Theater Program - Personal Papers, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Hurwitz, Leo, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - H-File, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Jaffe, Leo, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Jaffe, Leo: SOA Advisory Council Member, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Keiser, Dorie, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Lee, Phyllis: SOA Development, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - L-File, 1976-1980 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Legal Counsel, Office of NYU, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Light, Enoch: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - M-File, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226609 1
      - M-File, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - M-File, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - M-File, 1975-1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Maggin, Jane C.: VP for Administrative and Student Services, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Mailing: SOA Faculty - Dean David Oppenheim, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Haig Manoogian - Head of Undergraduate Studies, Department of Film and TV: Personal File, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Meetings, Development, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Meetings, Faculty SOA, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Meetings, Faculty, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Confidential: Tenure Materials - Charles Milne, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Musical Theater: Performance, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Musical Theater: Rodgers - Mauceri, Englander, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Oliva, L. Jay, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226610 9
      - Oliva, L. Jay, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Oliva Task Force: University Priorities, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Oral History of the Theater, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Memo to Vandament and Response to Martin Phillips Report, 0000 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Martin Phillips Report: Original - Final Draft, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Martin Phillips Report: Early Drafts (Oppenheim Drafts), undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Parent's Day, 1982-1985 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Personnel Directory TSOA, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Pineapple Dance Center, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Piscator, Maria, undated (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Point Count by Departments, 1971-1986 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Press, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Rackmil, Milton, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Radio Major, undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - Reiner, Geoffrey, undated (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Rodgers, Richard/Foundation: SOA Advisory Council Member, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Rosenberg, D., 1985 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Sabbatical Requests, 1983-1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        bar code#: 3 1142 04226611 7
      - Sabbatical Applications, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Samson, Lisa, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Schaffer, Andrew, 1982-1985 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Schechner, Richard, 1981-1986 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Schober, Joseph, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Seelmann, Jo, 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Sesquicentennial Programming, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Shubert Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Shubert Annual Reports, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Simon, Elena, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Stirk, David, 1980-1985 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Wank, Adams, Slavin, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Wank, Adams, Slavin, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 14)